MIGUEL NICOLAS DÍAZ VARGAS

Systems engineer

Bogotá, CO (11001)

Phone: +57 3238139902

Mail: nicolasdiazv1102@gmail.com

GitHub Profile

n LinkedIn Profile

</> Portfolio

Systems engineer in training with emphasis on **front end development** and web development skills. Experience in the use of technologies such as **Next.js**, **React** y **TailwindCSS**. I am committed to giving the best in each project through constant learning and adapting to new technologies.

SKILLS

Front-end development: Next.js | ReactJS | JS/TS | TailwindCSS | CSS | HTML

• Databases: MongoDB | SQL

• Other technologies: Git | Payload CMS

• Soft Skills: Integrity | Teamwork | Adaptability | Collaboration | Sense of Belonging

EXPERIENCE

• Full-stack Developer | Subdirección para la Juventud - Secretaría Distrital de Integración Social | Bogotá | 2024 - current

I contributed to the approach, documentation, design and development of the initial version of the new Distrito Joven website, defining its structure and key functionalities.

NextJS - ReactJS - ExpressJS - TailwindCSS - PostgresSQL

• Information Systematizer | Innquanta SAS | Bogotá | 2024 - current

Developed automation to collect and systematize baseline data and attendance records for impact evaluation analysis.

Google Apps Script

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Systems Engineering – Francisco Jose de Caldas District University,
 Bogotá – August 2020 – current

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- Four Parks NextJS, ReactJS, TailwindCSS 2024
 Construction of reservation platform and parking management from architecture to deployment. (GitHub repository)
- Dxter Shark NextJS, PayloadCMS, MongoDB 2023
 Development of a sports clothing purchasing platform with administrator mode using PayloadCMS, authentication and use of the ShadcnUI component library. (GitHub repository)